I'm Miyumi Ohta, from the Eco Room.
I'm Shiyoko Seiki
I am Sana Muramatsu
This is Kiwara Saito
Today I sent Captain Ryutobo.
I'm so happy!
I've really wanted to do this for a long time.
It's been a long time coming
Have you done it before?
Are you sure?
No, I haven't.
What if you haven't?
I've been on tour my whole life.
I can't believe it.
That's a lot of money.
I'm so bad at this, I don't even know if I can do it.
Today's my first time.
First time.
Oh, my God.
Please hold it down.
I'll do my best.
Today, we will divide into two teams, and the team with the most prizes of a given color will win.
The teams will be decided by drawing lots.
I'm looking forward to it!
What shall we do?
Seino
Video
Adult team
Children's team.
Children's team. Children's teams.
Dad, each team gets 10,000 yen.
Yay!
We'll have a time limit of 30 minutes.
Team wins.
I'm off! I'm off!
Let's go, let's go, let's go
Let's go!
Let's go for it
We can definitely win
Let's win!
Team
There was a little pink in there.
Yeah, yeah.
It's mainly pink.
I'm looking forward to it.
I've been wanting to play a really dark game lately.
I just went the other day.
Really?
I got something.
You got it?
I got some jagariko.
Cute jicaricos.
So cute!
There's a lot of them.
It looks like a lot, doesn't it?
Pink.
What's this?
This one's nice. Pink.
This one's nice.I like this one.
You want to do it?
Dokin-chan.
Boomer?
It's got pink in it.
Shall we do it?
Why don't you take this one down a little bit?
Okay, one at a time? You want to give it a shot?
Chiara's kind of funny.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God! That's great!
Oh, my God, that's amazing!
Oh, my God!
My head!
Oh, my head!
What?
That's great! I'm a little frustrated! I'm a little frustrated. Let's do it again.
I've never won one of these before, like this tableau.
I'm in luck today.
Go!
Oh, not at all!
I'm out.
Really?
Oh, my God.
I mean, you're making me so fat.
Am I a little off? Yeah, but...
Oh, my gosh!
Another one?
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, you're good! Wow, you're good!
Look at this! I feel like I'm going to be crushed by this!
Wow!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Oh, my God!
Is it going to come back in a new shape?
That's the first one!
Oh, my God!
That's great!
Oh, man, two and we're done?
new world
Oh, my God!
My head hurts! Like this one?
Okay, Kiara-san.
I'll try my best to take a picture.
Please do.
It's tiring, isn't it?
The task is a little short.
You're right, I have to put it in this gap.
Let's take a look at the others.
I'm off.
Team Light Blue
I'll do my best.
First time in your life, right?
I'd like to see the first one of my life and then I'll be there.
Which one's easier to photograph?
The light blue one, right?
Is the big one easier to photograph?
What? But boxes are a little harder to photograph. What? But it's kind of hard to find a box or something.
Do you ever have cinnamon?
One cinnamon stick?
Yeah.
That's cute.
Where can we go?
I don't know.
But it seems like half a second.
It's true.
Light blue.
Are you sure? Okay, then.
Let's give it a try.
You want to put the money in?
I'll put the money in.
What? It's a touch screen?
Oh, my God! They have touch screens now?
Can we just do it once?
Yeah, let's just do it once and then I can go away.
You're leaving? I'm so sad.
I'm gonna miss you.
First time! I'm going!
How do you do it?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
That's it. That's it.
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, wait a minute.
Can you do it?
Yeah, but just for a second.
It's okay.
Come on, come on, come on. what's up, what's up, what's up
It's so close! It's so close!
Here it comes... here it comes... here it comes...
I might be able to make it.
Well, good luck.
Don't leave me alone.
I didn't take the picture.
He left me alone.
I'd like to shoot something different.
I'll get it. I'm sure I'll get it. I think this one's a little easier.
Here we go. Please.
I'm just saying that I'd like to get some cinnamon pearls.
But I feel like I'm doing pretty good for my first time.
Come on!
This is how I spend my money. This is how I want it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
What am I supposed to do next time? I'll just go a little deeper.
Come on! Come on, come on, come on, come on!
No, no, no, no, no! What do I do?
Can you try looking at it from the side? I'll try the side view.
Maybe they're coming too fast.
I think I can make it.
I don't know what to do.
How can I get it?
Why are you giving up?
I'm going to go to the keychain place
I've spent all my money
I'll just keep playing as long as I have time. In the meantime, I'll do it as long as I have time.
I'll just go with Dokin-chan, since you're so close.
It's gonna be hard.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll give it a shot.
I'll try.
Go for it, Shimo!
It's okay.
Let's do it.
It's good.
Let's go to the sea.
from the top
Good job Hinde
You're losing to Kampeo!
Put a little bit of work into it.
prior cosa
I want to take it out, but it fell out.
I'm going to try a little amber salt.
Is it pink?
In the cheeks.
Oh, on the cheek.
Oh, my God.
I don't think I can get this off.
I don't know. It's a little too much.
I want to get the koacham.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm going crazy.I'm going crazy. This is crazy.
Oh, no.
If my aim is a little off...
I don't know, it's just not right.
Oh, it's okay.
Oh, no, it's not.
Uh-oh.
It's okay.
Bummer.
Last last last.
There's nothing I can use that many of them.
Oh, it's okay.
All right.
Ahh.
That's not fair.
I'm gonna go tease him.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Whew.
Oh, God.
I'm so mad at you.
Oh, look, the bottom.
Film me.
She's like, "I'm filming you.
I'm gonna get it.
I'm gonna give up, right? Let's just give up.
I'll take this one.
I put 500 yen in all at once, so here it is.
Wait, I've never done this before.
How do you do it?
Oh, that's how you adjust to the line.Oh, that's how you adjust to the line.
That's so hard.
Can you do it?
What's this?
This is kind of hard, I think I picked the wrong one.
But I put 500 yen in.
I'll give you 500 yen.
But I can't do this?
What do you mean?
Wait, wait, wait, wait. You're clearing it?
It's too hard.
And this is the first time I've ever done this.
What is this?
I don't know.
I misunderstood it a little bit, but I couldn't do it.
Downstairs.
Let's go somewhere else.
Baby registry.
Oh, my God.
Baby.
It's okay.
I think it's good.
I think you're on the right track.
I don't know where to put it.
Oh, my God, it's the neighbor.
The guy next to me.
He's talking so much.
Hey, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Wait, I think I got it.Wait, I think I got it.
Oh, no.
Come to my house!
Shin-chan.
Don't let go of me.
Why are you letting go?
Don't let go.
Once you hold on, you won't let go
It's in the lyrics.
There's a song by the Junkies called "Hold on and don't let go.
You've already let go, so I won't do it again.
I love it.
I'm in.
Me, too.
I don't know what to do.
Wait.
Hey, why are you grabbing me?
I made a mistake.
Are you gonna let go?
Don't let go.
Why would I let go?
Why are you letting go?
She's gone for the evening, and I'm just cheering.
I'm going.
Oh, no, no, no.
Okay, okay! Yes, I got it!
Pangyo-don!
Well, I'll take a picture of this my melody too!
Oh, wow!
I got it! Pangyo-don!I got it! Pangyo-don!
Cute!
Oh, I love it!
That's great!
They're keeping it for the shoot.
Let's go for it!
I'll do my best. I'm going to shoot this My Melo.
Okay, I'll do this one too, Shramon.
How many times are you going to do it?
A few.
Oh, my God!
Oh, here it comes.
Okay, here we go.
I'm gonna get it. I'm gonna get it.
You think we're gonna make it to page one? Here we go.
We can't go any deeper.
Here we go!
Oh, that's good, right?
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, no, no, no.
Ten more minutes.
I can't!
Wait a minute.
I took this.
I'll get it!
Hey, Chiara!
I got it!
I'm so happy!
And I got one too.And I got a shot too!
It was worth the effort!
He's so cute!
Next time!
Oh no, babies are so hard!
But you can't give up now, can you?
Baby!
Oh, it's up, but...
I was really scared!
But he's so cute.
Not too cute.
Don't get your hopes up.
Let's just go with it.
I don't know.
I don't care.
Someone take a picture!
Somebody take my picture!
Somebody take a picture!
What?
Oh, shit.
Somebody take my picture!
Somebody take a picture!
Okay, last one.
This is the UFO Catcher swamp.
It's going up so high, isn't it?We've come so far, haven't we?
It's going up so much.
Mmm.
This prawn bird is drawing it.
Oh, he's cute.
I think he likes prawns.
I want you to draw more prawn birds.
I'll draw it and try.
All right!
I'll go around.
It won't turn.
That's why I gave up.
I see.
I got pink.
I got pink in it.
Come on.
Please, please, please, please.
Please, please, please, please...
Oh, the money!
Oh, my God.
It's got pink in it.
I'm glad I got it.
I'm glad I didn't give up, because I'm giving it to Yuri-chan.
Yay!
Second one.
Let's key.
The one you didn't write is bearứentNot written bearứent
acai ぜろ不會
dare I'm in pain.
Help me.
I'm in pain.
Gabina I came here to fake it.
It's gone!
I want a white shark!
I love sharks!
I love sharks.
Please, I'm stuck.
Please, please, please, please, please.
Please, please, please, please, please, please.
Please, please, please, please.
Guys.
For two.
All right.
I'm totally hot.
I'm so hot!
It's so hot!
It's okay that the string is a water container.
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
Take it easy, take it easy.
I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it
I love, I love, I love, I love, I love.
I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love.
Come to my house.
Please, come to my house.Please, come to my house.
You're here.
Mimi's on three.
Mom guesses three.
I've got to try, too.
Wow!
I'm gonna roll!
Three lines of bye-bye.
I'd feel better if I took something secure.
I'll feel more secure.
I wish you the best of luck, My Melo!
Ah! The guy in front! The guy in front!
Wait, isn't this our chance?
Isn't this a good chance?
Let's go take a look.
Oh, I didn't quite get it.
Ah! Aah! Aah!
Wait, wait, wait! I got it, I got it!
Aah! Aah!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
It's not pink!
We can still do it twice more.
I got two green ones from the Red Oak.
Aah!
Oh, I think the Razz Sampler has more pink in it.
I don't know, who eats and rolls on top of each other?
Oh, but it might work! I'll give it a try.
I've always wanted to do this on YouTube. I wanted to do this, I wanted to do this, I wanted to do this on YouTube.
I just want to do this.
I just want to do it.
Wow, that's great!
I'll do it.
Oh, wait!
Isn't it dangerous?
Oh, it's not bad?
Oh, thank God!
I'm so happy!
I think we hit it.
Oh, my God!
Aaaaah!
I guess that means you're a genius.
Wow!
Oh, my gosh! Really!
But, you could have won this one, couldn't you?
Oh, no!
Pink team!
We've redone it!
I think we're pretty confident now.
It's a simple graffiti for both of us.
How could I?
I've already done my part for the first time.
The first one?
Finished?
Maybe I'm a genius.
Boo-hoo! I can't do it, Aqua... it's not my style.
You'd have a better life on your own.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you... I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
It's gonna be okay. Armrina's gonna be okay.
Don't worry, don't worry
Group!
I have to decide 5 times that I'm not into you... so I have to pick you up 5 more times?
I'm going to have to pick you up five more times.
Mirinyah, I got it!
How did you do that?
That's great!
It's going to be dyed light blue.
Don't worry, I'll live.
I'm going to die!
I think we can get the little one, right?
Let's go.
Okay, give me a kiss.
Catch!
Please!
Oh, so sharp!
Oh, no!
But I think I can do better than a stuffed animal.
Scintillating!
What?
Tough world!
It's okay, it's light blue.
It's a little bit light blue.
This is the moment.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on, come on, come on. Come on, come on, come on.
It's going this way.
This one's going to work, too, right?
I'm right on target.
Aah!
Aah! That's gonna work.
Yeah!
You know what, it's not time.
I'm ready to go now.
I can go. I can go.
These are the moments.
Can you go?
I'm going.
I'm right on target.
I can't go.
I can't go. I can't go.
I can't go. I can't go. I can't go.
Wait! I'm in a hurry! I'm in a hurry!
I'm in a hurry
Time is sometimes...
Three hundred.
Wait a minute.
Oh, no.
Zero.
Go!
Yamaguchi koei!
Oh, that's close.
You can do it.
Is it too late?Can't do it anymore?
I can't do it anymore.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Go for it.
You have one minute.
One minute?
But miracles do happen.
Money?
You want some money?
You want 100 yen?
Sure, spend 100 yen.
Okay?
I'm going to go after him.
Oh, no.
I can't do it anymore.
I've only got 200 yen left.
I don't know if I can do it.
I might not make it.
I'm afraid so.
I've only got a hundred left.
That's when the power comes out.
That's when you really show your stuff.
I'm that kind of person.
Well, miracles do happen, don't they?
Yes, sir.
Miracles didn't happen.
Bye bye.
The time has come and gone and the money is gone...Yes, the time has come and gone, and the money has run out, so we're done.
The end
That was a lot of pokes!
Millenia...
What's that?
Huh?
Why is this zero?
I'm so sorry.
I tried my best, but it was really hard.
But it was super fun.
That's great!
I think it's really great that you got this much for the first time in your life.
You know, you did great.
I'm curious to see how many the other team got.
I feel like we can win.
I'll wait for the results!
So here's what we got, and here's what each of us got!
These are different colors.
There are so many!
Let's start with the light blue team.
No, no, no...
The light blue Hangyodan.
I took this one.
Next.
One more! Next!
Next!
And and and and and and and and and and...
Oh, it's so cute!
A bowhead shark! A bowhead shark!
That mouth... that mouth is amazing!
You're right, it's coming off.
I took this one too.
I don't know, they're both like that.
Next!
What's that? This tag is light blue.
There it is!
It's a basking shark!
Amazing!
I took this one too.
That's great!
And this part is light blue.
White shark!
That's great!
I took this one.
That's great. For the first time in my life, I got four of these.
That's great!
I'm getting so good at this.
That's great.
So I got four.
Four!
The pink team's bowhead shark.
What's that? What's that? What's that?
Huh? What's that?
Actually, you know what?
Huh?
Ta-da!
Aah!Aah!
Aah! I don't have any!
I was pretty close, but I didn't get anything.
I'm so sorry.
But it was fun, right? It was fun.
Okay, then.
Okay. Okay.
Okay, now let's go to the pink team.
Great, I want to see it right away.
Okay, well, I got this one first.
Hey!
Wait!
The one we didn't get.
Oh, my God!
Wow! Oh, man! This!
It's just so different!
Oh, man! Wait!
It's a little heavy.
Oh, yeah, yeah, that?
Whoa!
Aah! I quit!
Oh, my God, I quit.
Pink. Where's the pink?
There it is! Caution!
Beware of scalding hot water!
Oh, pink.
Maybe he didn't really move it.
Oh, hey, that's great.
Still so-so, so-so.
I did my best. This, uh, spinning thing. I did my best. This, uh, spinning thing.
Oh, my gosh!
The hardest one.
Wow, you got it!
And here's the next one!
Oh, that's great!
And, ta-da!
Oh, it's so cute!
It's so cute!
I took this one next to Sanatun's half-fish bowl!
Too cute!
So cute!
And here it is!
Oh, what?
There were a lot of them around here.
Oh, my God, wait!
I got it. I got it too, but I didn't bring it with me. That's part of it, right?
Just in case.
It's pink.
Oh, does that count?
Oh, just in case.
And finally, here it is.
Oh, my God. What?
Oh, my God! I bought this at a convenience store.
Oh, my God!
Did you just drop it, Papa?
I was so sad, all I got was green all the time.
But it's got green-pink in it.
Oh, really!
It's got pink in it. It's got pink in it.
It really is!
That's, that's good. I'm saying tags and stuff too.
Oh, wow, that's great.
I only took this one from this compoteur.
I knew it. It's getting better and better.
That's great.
That's great. That's really great.
That's great!
You're right.
Oh, my God!
You want to do 30 kilometers?
That's great.
The pink team got 13 in 30 minutes!
Yay!
That was amazing.
That's great!
It's a victory!
So, the winning team gets one of the losing team's prizes.
Oh, really?
Take your pick.
What would you like?
Okay, well, let's see...
I have the most open mouth.
Oh, okay.
Shark?
Oh, shark! Shark!
Go for it.
It's open.It's open.
Yes, so I got my wish to play UFO catcher and got a lot!
Yay!
See you later, I thought I'd like to do it when I have a chance.
Thanks for watching!
Bye bye!
No!
Hey, stop!
Well, okay.
No!